Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: \[01/11/2024\] This Privacy Policy governs the use of the services provided by FUNNOW GROUP(hereinafter also referred to as "we", "our" or "us"), either itself or through its Eatigo operated subsidiaries, via various electronic platforms such as the Eatigo website or mobile site (i.e. www.Eatigo.com) (the "Eatigo Sites") or mobile applications (the "Mobile Apps") (the Eatigo Sites, Mobile Apps and the services offered and/or provided thereon shall collectively hereinafter be referred to as the "Services"). By using the Services in any manner (whether as a registered user or otherwise), you therefore agree that you have read this Privacy Policy and accept the terms stated herein. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy, without notice, at any time. You understand that your continued use of the Services after this Privacy Policy has been modified constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as amended. For the avoidance of doubt, this Privacy Policy shall also apply to our Merchants (as defined below), as users of the Services and/or Account (as defined below) holders. If this Privacy Policy is modified in any way it will be updated [here](https://eatigo.com/privacy-policy). Regularly checking and reviewing this page ensures that you are updated on the information which may be collected, used (and under what circumstances), and if it may be shared with other parties (if at all). If we believe that the modifications are material, we will notify you of the changes by posting a notice on the Eatigo Sites and/or the Mobile Apps, or email you at the email address provided to us by you, and as we may deem appropriate. What constitutes a material change will be determined by us, at our sole and absolute discretion. We are committed to protecting your privacy, and we hope that this Privacy Policy demonstrates our commitment to fair information practices, and that this Privacy Policy gives confidence to use the Services. **1\. About this privacy policy and our services** This Privacy Policy supplements our Terms of Use (or “Terms”, and which may be found at [here](https://eatigo.com/terms-of-use)), and your use of the Services are therefore governed by both this Privacy Policy and the Terms. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle information collected and received by us from you during the course of your use of the Services. It also governs the collection, use and disclosure of your information and Personal Data (as defined below). We therefore strongly recommend that you read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices with regard to the collection and/or usage of your information and Personal Data. This privacy policy is only applicable to the Services and not to any other website(s), mobile site(s), mobile application(s) and/or application(s) that you may be able to access from the Services (whether through an advertisement, service, or content link) or any website or mobile site of our Merchants or affiliates, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. While you may use the Services (and part(s) thereof) without registration, many of the content and Services on the Eatigo Sites or Mobile Apps require registration. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the information and Personal Data you provide to us. Inaccurate information and Personal Data will affect the information you receive when using the Services, our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy, and which would be crucial to the performance of the Services and your receipt of the benefit(s) thereunder. **2\. Information and Personal Data we collect from you** "Personal Data" means any data about an individual who can be identified from that data. It includes without limitation an individual’s personal information such as their first and last name, contact details such as your email address and telephone number, year of birth, age, account username and password, credit card information and your address. Further to the above, information and Personal Data may also include the following: a. Particulars of your social media accounts (such as gender, birthdate, profession and/or location) if any such account is connected to our App and/or Website; and b. Any other personal information which may be provided by you or any third parties in connection with the provision of the Services and/or your usage of the App and/or Website. c. When you use any of the features and functions available on the Services; d. When you visit the Eatigo Sites or use the Mobile Apps, we may from time to time also automatically receive and record information from your browser or mobile device, including your Traffic Data (as defined below), Cookies, Web Beacons and other data; and e. If you contact us, for example, with an enquiry or to report an issue. After registering for an Account with us, you may update your Account details by logging into your Account, clicking on the link to your Account details and thereafter following the applicable directions. We may also process your other information and Personal Data, such as: a. Particulars of your social media accounts (such as gender, birthdate, profession and/or location) if any such account is connected to our App and/or Website; and b. Any information you may send to us or our Merchants or affiliates who use the Services; and c. Transactional history, in order to document a transaction you may have had with us and/or third parties. Also, if you give us information about another person, then you confirm that you can: a. Give consent on his/her behalf for the collection and/or processing of his or her Personal Data; b. Receive on his/her behalf any notices; and c. Warrant that you have obtained his/her consent for us or have the right to allow us to collect, store and/or otherwise use his/her Personal Data. Even if you do not register for an Account, we collect non-personal information about your use of our Eatigo Sites in the following manners: a. Cookies A Cookie is a small data file sent from a website to your browser that is stored on your device. Cookies are used for a number of purposes, including to display the most appropriate content based on your interests and activity on the Services, estimate and report the Services’ total audience size and traffic, and conduct research to improve the Services. You can configure your device's settings to reflect your preference to accept or reject Cookies. If you reject all Cookies, you will not be able to enjoy the full range of the Services. We therefore use Cookies to customize your experience on the Eatigo Sites. For example, if your password is stored via a Cookie, you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Eatigo Sites We do not link the information stored in Cookies to any of your information and Personal Data you submit while on the Eatigo Sites. Some of our affiliates also use Cookies to provide us with anonymous data and information regarding your use of the Eatigo Sites, Mobile Apps and the Services. We do not have access or control over these Cookies, and this Privacy Policy does not therefore govern the use of such Cookies. b. Web Beacons Web Beacons are tiny graphic image files embedded in a web page or email that provide a presence on the web page or email and send back to its home server information from the user's browser. We or our third party tracking utility company also use Web Beacons to collect anonymous information about your use of the Eatigo Sites and the websites of selected sponsors and advertisers, and your use of emails, special promotions or newsletters we send to you. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of the Eatigo Sites or Mobile Apps, or those of our sponsors' or advertisers’. We do not link your non-personal information from Web Beacons to your information and Personal Data without your permission, except in connection with our marketing, promotion, or similar initiatives jointly with our Merchants and affiliates, if any. c. Traffic Data We automatically track and collect the following categories of information, amongst others, when you visit and/or access the Eatigo Sites or Mobile Apps: (1) Internet Protocol (“IP”) address; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers; (4) types of web browsers used; (5) referring source which may have sent you to the Eatigo Sites or Mobile Apps; and (6) other information associated with the interaction of your browser and the Eatigo Sites (collectively "Traffic Data"). We may link non-personal information from traffic data to personal information, when you register an account with us. **3\. How we use the information and Personal Data we collect** a. Account Registration We use the information and Personal Data that you provide to respond to your questions, provide you the Services, offer you our Merchants’ services and send you emails that are necessary or that we think may interest you. You may choose not to provide us with any information or Personal Data and in such a case you can still access and use some of the Services; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Services that require your information and Personal Data upon, and especially the registration of an Account with us. b. Enquiries Subject to this Privacy Policy, if you contact us, we may use any of the information and Personal Data you provide in connection with your enquiry, or any information, Personal Data and non-personal information when responding to your enquiries. c. Our Emails to you We may use your contact details to send you information when necessary, including Account verification emails, and in conjunction with your use of the Services. In some cases, when you click on a link or an advertisement in an email, your browser may be momentarily directed to the website of a third party which, acting on our behalf (see below), notes or "counts" your response to the email before redirecting your browser to your selected destination; this redirection process may not be apparent to you. d. Market Research From time to time our market research department, or our contractors and affiliates acting on our behalf, may conduct online research in order to gather feedback about our Eatigo Sites, Mobile Apps and the Services. This may be done through email invitations, pop-up surveys, online focus groups, and social networks. When participating in such feedback, we may ask you to submit your information and Personal Data. Your information and Personal Data may be used for research purposes. When a survey is sponsored by an affiliate or other third party, aggregate information of the survey results is reported to the sponsor. Information and Personal Data collected through market research will be used only by us, our affiliates, our service providers and contractors, and successors and assigns, and will not otherwise be given or sold to another third party without your consent or as otherwise permitted by this Privacy Policy. We will not knowingly accept survey responses from or conduct interviews with any person under the age of 18. In addition to collecting survey responses from our users, Cookies may be used to authenticate respondents or to help you pick up where you left off in a survey. If you have Cookies disabled you may not be able to participate in some surveys. Cookies may be used to connect survey data with our Eatigo Sites’ usage characteristics. You will be notified when we would like to use Cookies in this way and your consent will be requested for these Cookies. e. Merchant Feedback We will collect feedback from our restaurant and dining service providers (“Merchants”) about our users, and vice versa, in order to protect the property and rights of the Merchants (including their company and/or business), to protect the safety of the public, restaurant employees or any person, or to prevent or end activity we consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. **4\. Information collected by third parties** Certain content and services offered to you through the Eatigo Sites and Mobile Apps are on websites hosted and operated by a company other than us or our affiliates ("Third Party Websites"). We do not disclose your information and Personal Data to these Third Party Websites without your consent, but you should be aware that any information you disclose once you access these other websites is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third Party Websites. You should review the privacy policy posted on any other website to understand how that Third Party Website collects and uses your information and Personal Data. **5\. Transfer and/or disclosure of your information** The information collected from you may be transferred, stored, and processed in any country in which we operate. By using the Services, you authorise us to use your information and Personal Data we operate for the purposes mentioned above. We will ensure that your information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and protected in accordance with applicable laws related to personal data protection . We may also transfer information about you to another company in connection with a merger, sale or acquisition. In this event, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. We do not, sell, rent or trade your information and Personal Data with any third parties for their marketing purposes, without your explicit consent. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Data as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Eatigo Sites and/or Mobile Apps. We share feedback provided about you by our Merchants and with the other Merchants that you may dine with through us in order to ensure the best possible experience for all parties involved. We also share certain categories of information we collect from you and about you from our affiliates and Merchants in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We may also share your information, Personal Data and Traffic Data with our affiliates and Merchants and other third parties who assist us by performing core services (such as business consulting and continuity planning, marketing, promotion, data analytics, data processing, hosting, storage and security) and/or by making certain Services available to our users. These affiliates, Merchants and other third parties are bound by the same and/or are required to uphold the comparable standards of security and confidentiality as particularised in the terms of this Privacy Policy, and they will use your contact data and other personal information to carry out their obligations to and to provide you with the related Services (e.g. dining services). For the avoidance of doubt, you agree that Merchants may (with our prior written consent) use your information or Personal Data for their own marketing and/or promotional efforts. The Merchant' use of your information or Personal Data shall, at all times, still be compliant with the relevant and applicable local laws . You may communicate the termination of the account, withdrawal of your consent to the continued use, disclosure, deletion of your personal data by clicking on ‘delete account' from your profile page or contacting us via dpo@Eatigo.com, subject to the conditions and/or limitations imposed by applicable laws or regulations. Please be aware that on receiving your request, we may retain your Personal Data for a given period of time for compliance with applicable laws and internal policies for the following purposes: to reply to inquiries; to resolve disputes or collect fees; to detect and deter fraudulent use of, or abuse of, our Services; or to comply with applicable law **6\. Indemnification** You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold us and our Affiliates harmless from all liabilities, claims, damages, losses, and expenses, including attorneys' fees that arise from your use of the Services (including the Eatigo Sites and Mobile Apps). We at our sole and absolute discretion reserve the right, at your expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate with us in asserting any available defenses. **7\. Security** The information and Personal Data we collect about you is stored on a secure, password-protected server and only authorised personnel have access to such information. We use industry-standard encryption technologies with respect to the receipt and transfer of your information and the Personal Data you submit to us on the Eatigo Sites and/or Mobile Apps. Nevertheless, and despite our best efforts, no transmission over the internet and no data storage method can be guaranteed to be safe 100% of the time. You also acknowledge and agree that it is important that you protect against unauthorised access of your Account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and Account secure (e.g. by signing out after using our Services). **8\. Contact us** If you wish to request access or request correction of your information or Personal Data, or if you wish to stop receiving emails from us, or if you have any questions, complaints, concerns or comments on our Privacy Policy, we welcome you to contact the Eatigo Data Protection Officer by sending an email to dpo@Eatigo.com or by contacting us via our Customer Support Page.

Download App

About Eatigo

Policies

Support

Partner with Eatigo

© 2024 Zoek. All rights reserved.
